## MAHAK GAUTAM

### mahakgautam02@gmail.com

+91-90752-20149





### Student

### Parvati Paytha, Pune 411009, Maharashtra





I am a coding enthusiast with strong problem-solving abilities and the ability to work well in groups. I am committed to developing my professional skills and expertise. My ambition is to reach higher levels in my career by doing meaningful work in the industry of IT.

### **EDUCATION**

• B.E. (Computer Engineering) Pune Vidhyarthi Griha's College of Engineering and Technology, Pune 9.65 CGPA 2021 - Current

• HSC (Science) G.B.M.M. Jr. College, Hinganghat

94.7% February 2020

 SSC Mahesh Gyanpeeth High School , Hinganghat 92.00 % March 2018

### SKILLS

- Technical Skills: Python, C++, Java, HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, JavaScript, PHP
- Developer Tools: GitHub, GitLab, JIRA, Figma, Canva, MS Office
- Databases & Framework: MySql, MongoDB, Bootstrap, Django, React JS,
- Soft Skills: Team Work And Collaboration, Time Management, Task Management, Self Motivated, Multitasking
- Coursework: OOPS, DBMS, CN, OS, DS/AI/ML
- Areas of Interest: Front-end Web Development, UI/UX

### **EXPERIENCE**

Knowledge Solution India

· Explored and visualized the data

• Identify patterns and correlations between features and the target variable

**Machine Learning Intern** 

Sep2021 - Dec2021

· Quencil Private limited, Noida

Web Developer Intern

• Front-end code development of a game review website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Dec2022 - Feb2023

Worked on UI \UX part and improve website usability.

Newton's Apple, Pune

- Design UI for Project VUMAS using Figma
- Use PHP, HTML, CSS for Implementing Front -end of project
- PiHole Dashboard Analysis
- ML Algorithm for URL ANALYSIS.

### Front-End Developer Intern June2023 -Current

### **PROJECTS**

- PERSONAL PORTFOLIO SITE
- **ELECTRONIC GADGET PRICE PREDICTION**
- HEART DISEASE PREDICTION **USING ML WITH PYTHON**
- GAMES USING PYTHON(TKINTER)
- GAME REVIEW WEBSITE & **QUENCIL COMPANY WEBSITE**
- IMAGE GALLERY PROJECT IN **DJANGO**

# **CERTIFICATES**

- 100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp (UDEMY)
- HTML & CSS in Depth (META)
- CPP, JAVA, LATEX, PYTHON (Spoken Tutorial)
- Principles of UI / UX Designing (META)
- Azure Al Fundamentals (MICROSOFT)
- Soft Skill Development Program (TATA TECHNOLOGIES)
- Djano , MySql (Great Learning)
- Cybersecurity Awareness Training Program (Quick Heal Academy )
- Complete Web Development Course (Coursera, UDEMY, VLABS)



## **AWARD**

### **LILA GIRL 2020**

2020 Lila Poonawalla Foundation Scholarship Winner



### A CLUBS

- DOCUMENTATION HEAD VLAB's PVGCOET
- DESIGN & PRODUCTION HEAD **GDSC PVGCOET**
- MEMBER OF EVENT TEAM **ACES PVGCOET**